ILGWU Political Department Records 5780/103
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Minimum Wage, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Muskie Election Committee, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- "N" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- National Consumers League, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- National Municipal League, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- National Sharecroppers, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- New York City (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Office of Economic Opportunity, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- March 5 OED Meeting Notes (Box 14, Folder 8)
- March 26 OED Meeting Notes (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Occupational Health and Safety, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- "P" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- P.E.D. Meetings (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Politics, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Price Control, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  February 9
- "R" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Registration, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- S. 3598 The Retirement Income Security for Employees Act, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  August 7
- Revenue Sharing, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  May 19
- Rural Development, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- "S" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Senate - General, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Replies from Senators on S. 1177 (Consumer Protection Agency Bill), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Replies from Senators on S. 1861, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Social Security - General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Student Loan Program, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- "T" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Taxes, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- "U" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Union Articles, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Unemployment Articles, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Unity House, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  June
- "X, Y, Z" General, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- "W" General, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- G.E.B. Reports, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Inter-Office, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Political Department Invoices, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Central States Region, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Cloak Joint Board and Cloak Out-of-Town, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Eastern Region, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Midwest Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Midwest Region, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Form Letters, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- New York City Locals, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Northeast Department, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Southeast Region, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Region, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Maryland Delegation (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Upper South Region, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Western States, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- January, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- February, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- March, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- April, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- May, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- June, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- July, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- August, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- September, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- October, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- November, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- December, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Cope Political Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO General, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- "A" General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Cope General, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO IUD General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO News, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- "B" General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- "C" General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Letters, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  In English and Spanish
- Congress, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Congress, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Congress, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Energy Policy Task Force (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Consumer Assembly, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Citizens Union, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Civil Rights, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Cope Operating Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- "D" General, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Day Care, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Democratic National Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Democratic Party, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Democratic Study Group, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- "E" General, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Personal, 1965-1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- "F" General, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Federationist, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Frontlash, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- "G" General, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Gus - Staff Mailings, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- "H" General, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Health Security, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- "I" General, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Congressional Breakfast (Letters of Thanks from Congressmen), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- ILGWU 75th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Message from President Gerald R. Ford, ILGWU 75th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  May 27
- Issues, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- "J" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- "K" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- "L" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Department of Labor, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Legislative Newsletter, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Lobbying Report (Evelyn Dubrow), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- "M" General, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Clarence Mitchell Luncheon, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- "N" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- NAACP, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- National Civic Review, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- National Consumer League, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- National Sharecroppers, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- The City Club of New York, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- "O" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- "P" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Post Card Registration, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- The Social Democrat, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Fall
- Puerto Rico Federation of Labor, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- "R" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Rice Production Act of 1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Charlotte Roe, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Charlotte Roe - Lobbying Report, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- "S" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Senate - General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- "T" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- "U" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- "W" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- White House Conference on Aging, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- "X, Y, Z" General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- AFL-CIO News, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- AFL-CIO News, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Justice, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Campaign Committee Receipt Book, 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Pamphlets (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Campaign Committee Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Contributions, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Contributions, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Campaign Material, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Campaign Contributions, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Receipt Book, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Campaign Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Voter Registration Posters (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Recent Campaign Laws (booklet), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Reports, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Registration Amendments, 1973-1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Campaign Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Campaign Regulations, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Committee for a Responsible Government, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Replies from Retirees on Election Letter, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Lists of Contributions, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Contributions, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Inter-Office, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Political Department Invoices, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Form Letters, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Central States, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Eastern Region, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Midwest Region, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- New England Region, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- New York City Locals, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- New York State, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Northeast Department, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Puerto Rico, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Upper South, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Southeast Region, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Western States Region, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- January, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- February, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- March, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- April, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- May, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- June, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- July, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- August, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- September, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- October, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- November, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- December, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- "A" General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Cope Area Conferences, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Cope General, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO General, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Cope - Political Memos, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Cope Area Conferences, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO IUD General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO News, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- "B" General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- "C" General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Governor Carey Campaign, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- CETA, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Civil Rights, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Congress, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Replies from Congressmen on 807, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Consumer Assembly, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- "D" General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Democratic National Committee, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Evelyn Dubrow Lobbying Expenses, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- "F" General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Federationist, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Pamela Freer's Lobbying Expenses, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Frontlash, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- "G" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- "H" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Health, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Health, Education, and Welfare Department, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- "I" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Employer Associations Special Meeting, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Luncheon Meeting for Congressman Joseph S. Ammerman, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Luncheon Meeting for Congressman Charles Rangel, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Meeting on Trade, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- "J" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- "K" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- "L" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Labor Law Reform, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Legislative Newsletter, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Letters to Retirees on Labor Law Reform, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Lobbying Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- "M" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- "N" General, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- National Civic Review, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- "J" General, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- "K" General, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- "L" General, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Legislative Bulletin, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Lobbying Reports, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Legislative Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Evelyn Dubrow Lobbying Expenses, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Pamela Freer Lobbying Expenses, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- "M" General, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The MacNeil-Lehrer Report, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  "American Business in Mexico"
- The Majority Report, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- "N" General, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- National Consumers League, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- National Civic Review, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Replies from Senators on National Health Insurance, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- New York City, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- New York State, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Committee on the Present Danger, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- "R" General, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- "S" General, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Letters Requesting Contributions for Senator Moynihan's Campaign, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Invitations to Moynihan Luncheon, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Senate - General, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- "J" General, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- "U" General, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- "V" General, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- "W" General, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Washington - General, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Washington Union Women (Box 22, Folder 24)
- White House Conference on Aging, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO News, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO News, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Justice, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- DNC Domestic Task Force, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- George Meany Center Oral History Interview with Evelyn Dubrow, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Democratic National Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Democratic National Committee Memorandums, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Winograd Commission Reports, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Delegates and Alternatives to the 1974 Conference on Democratic Party Organization and Policy (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Democratic National Party Conference - Arrangements Committee, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- "Marginal State Legislative Races in Key Reapportionment States", 1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Congressional Reapportionment Project
- Checks and Receipts, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Checks and Receipts, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Checks and Receipts, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Checks and Receipts, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Congressional Black Caucus, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Congress, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Letters to Congressmen on Bills H.R. 4006 - H.R. 6687, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Form Letters, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- G.E.B. Reports, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Inter-Office, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Political Department Invoices, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Central States Region, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Midwest Region, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- New England Region, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- New Jersey Region, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- New York City Locals, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- New York State, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Northeast, Western Pennsylvania, and Ohio Department, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rico, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Upper South Department, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Western States, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- January, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- February, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- March, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- April, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- May, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- June, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- July, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- August, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- September, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- December, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- "A" General, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- "B" General, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO General, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO Cope General, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Cope Area Conferences, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Marginal Districts, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Cope House Marginal Committee Report, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Cope Political Memos, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- AFL-CIO News, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO IUD, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Trade Bill, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- "C" General, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Civil Rights, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Carter-Mondale, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Consumers for Carter-Mondale, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Carter Statement, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  January 15
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Flyers and Posters, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Campaign Literature, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Consumer Assembly, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- "D" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Democratic National Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- "E" General, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Economic Consulting Services, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Equal Rights Amendment, 1970-1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- New York State Equal Rights Amendment, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Equal Rights Amendment, 1970-1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- "F" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Federationist, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Frontlash, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- "G" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Housing, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- "I" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Legislative/Political Conference, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  January 3-5
- H.R. 10853 - to amend Tariff Act of 1974, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Issues (Box 25, Folder 28)
- "J" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- "K" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Korean Conference, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- "L" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Legislative Bulletin, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Lobbying Reports, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Evelyn Dubrow Lobbying Expenses, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Pamela Freer Lobbying Expenses, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- "M" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- "N" General, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- NAACP, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- National Civic Review, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Seating List for Frank W. McCulloch Luncheon, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- National Consumer League, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- H.R. 13541 National Employment Priorities Act, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- "O" General, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- "P" General, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Pension Offset, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- "R" General, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- "S" General, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Senate - General, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- "T" General, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- H.R. 9937 - to exempt the textile and apparel industries from tariff cuts, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- "U" General, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Letters to Washington, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- White House Conference, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Letters to Washington, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- H.R. 3919 Windfall Profits Tax, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- "X, Y, Z" General (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Justice, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO News, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Posters (Box 26, Folder 21)
- January, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- February, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- March, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- April, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- May, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- June, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- July, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- August, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- September, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- October, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- November, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- December, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- "A" General, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO News, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- "B" General, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- January, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- February, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- March, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- April, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- May, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- June, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- July, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- August, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- September, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- October, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- November, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- December, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- "A" General, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO General, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Action Bulletins, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Cope General, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO IUD General, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alerts, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO News Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Bankruptcy Act Proposals, 1973-1981 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- "B" General, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Bills and Amendments, 1974-1980 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Bills and Amendments, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Budget Coalition Statement, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- "C" General, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Central States Region, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Agency for Child Development, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Coalition for Labor Union Women, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Committees, 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Congress, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Congressional Black Caucus, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Consumer Assembly, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Cope Area Conferences, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Cope Financial Reports, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Cope Operating Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Cope Political Memos, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- "D" General, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Democratic National Committee, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Democratic Party, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- "E" General, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Electoral College Reform, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Employer Associations, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Personal, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Congratulation Letters to Evelyn Dubrow about Vice-Presidency, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Import Speeches - Evelyn Dubrow (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Evelyn Dubrow Speeches, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Evelyn Dubrow Statement Before the Subcommittee of Labor, HEW Appropriations Committee, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  April 20
- "F" General, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Facts About Congress, 1975-1981 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Federationist, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Form Letters, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Pamela Freer Expenses, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Frontlash, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- "G" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- GEB Report from Washington, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- GOP Communications, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- "H" General, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Health, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Hobbs Act Campaign, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Homework, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- "I" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Statement on Unemployment Compensation, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Immigration, 1975-1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Imports, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Inter-Office, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- "J" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- "K" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- RFK Memorial, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- "L" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Labor - General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Legislative Alerts, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Legislative Bulletin, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Legislative Newsletters, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Legislative Newsletter Lists, 1977-1981 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Legislative Representatives, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Lobbying Reports, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- "M" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Midwest Region, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Minimum Wage, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- "N" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- NAACP, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- National Consumers League, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- New York City Locals, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- New England Region, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- New Jersey Region, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- New York State, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Northeast, Western Pennsylvania, and Ohio Department, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- New York Festival, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- "O" General, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- "P" General, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Departmental Invoices, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- "Q" General, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- "R" General, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Replies from Congressmen on Minimum Wage Letters, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Right-to-Work Literature, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)